# Davis Land

#### **PROFILE**

Current student of telecommunications, media studies, and computer science with experience in broadcasting, publishing, and event organizing. Passionate about artistic storytelling and providing a voice where one may not exist.

510 Thornton Ct. College Station, TX, 77840 (903) 920-9269 dland95@tamu.edu davisland.info

#### EXPERIENCE

#### KANM Student Radio, College Station, TX

#### Programming Director - December 2014 to Present

• Oversee show scheduling, FCC compliance, DJ attendance and show logs.

#### DJ - September 2013 to Present

Produce weekly two hour radio show. Conduct interviews in-studio with bands.

# KEOS Community Radio, Bryan, TX - DJ/Volunteer - August 2014 to Present

- Produce two weekly two hour radio shows.
- Review music for library inclusion and air play.

### Write About Now, Houston, TX - Producer, Podcast Host - December 2014 to Present

- Assist in audio and video recording for the Write About Now YouTube channel and podcast.
- Produce half-hour podcast featuring poets at a weekly poetry slam in Houston, TX, submit to iTunes.

#### Mic Check Poetry, Bryan, TX - Vice President, CFO - March 2014 to Present

- Coordinate and ensure effective action pertaining to Mic Check's 5or(c)(3) non-profit and financial status.
- Assist President in duties such as management of the Texas Grand Slam Poetry Festival and various Arts Council
  programs.

#### The Eckleburg Project, Texas A&M's Student Literary Journal, College Station, TX

#### Poetry Editor and Officer - May 2014 to Present

- Lead and manage poetry team in selecting the poetry sections of each semester's journal.
- Work with officer board to plan for each semester as well as make decisions pertaining to the future of the magazine.

#### Poetry Screener - September 2013 to May 2014

- Select the poetry section of each semester's journal from a pool of submitted student writing.
- Staff and contribute to poetry workshops held on-campus.

# Mostly Water, Independent Literary Journal, Bryan, TX - Editor-In-Chief, Founder - October 2014 to Present

- Coordinate with staff in designing, curating and editing the journal, maintaining online brand and presence.
- Manage local, statewide, national, and international direct distribution and bookstore distribution.

#### Target, College Station, TX - Trainer and Team Member- December 2014 to Present

- Arrive before store opening to unload delivery truck, stock store with merchandise.
- Oversee stocking team in training and effective day-to-day operation.

#### Chick-fil-A, Whitehouse, TX - Team Leader and Closer, Cashier - May 2010 to August 2013

 Assist night managers in store operation and closing procedures, ensure team members are taking and fulfilling orders efficiently, ensure guest satisfaction.

# EDUCATION AND AWARDS/HONORS

Texas A&M University

B.S. Telecommunications and Media Studies; Minor: Computer Science

Major GPA: 3.0, Overall GPA: 2.8; Expected Graduation: December 2017

Excellence in Broadcasting Journalism Award Earned for outstanding work in Whitehouse High School's Broadcasting Journalism program.

Eagle Scout Earned Eagle rank in the spring of 2013.

## **SKILLS**

Highly skilled in Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, and Premiere. Proficient in Adobe Illustrator. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Excel, and Powerpoint. Experience and skill in audio/visual editing, graphic design, and document layout. Familiar with various hardware tools in audio/video recording and production as well as applicable techniques. Experience with C++, Python, HTML, CSS, and XML coding languages.

#### Davis Land 510 Thornton Ct. College Station, TX, 75703 • (903) 920-9269 • dland 95@tamu.edu

# **REFERENCES**

Erin Holesher; <u>Station Manager</u>, KANM Student Radio erinrose922@gmail.com; (210) 845 - 0465

 $\label{eq:Florence Davies} \textbf{Florence Davies}; \underline{Administrator}, \textbf{The Texas A&M University Writing Center}; \underline{Advisor}, \textbf{The Eckleburg Project fsdaviesog@tamu.edu; (281) 658-3627}$ 

Brady Ware; Videographer, Write About Now Poetry

brady@softwaysolutions.com; (979) 421 - 3556

Bill Moran; Former President, Mic Check Poetry

 $billmoran 68@gmail.com; (218)\ \mathring{4}67\ -\ 4654$